<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-10-26T06:35:18+00:00</updated><id>https://lizainslie.dev/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Lizzy’s Blog</title><subtitle>Welcome to my little corner of the internet! Here, I write about whatever I feel like writing. I mostly enjoy writing about tech, humor, and music, but I try not to limit myself to just a few things. I am transgender (MTF), and 18 years of age.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Today, Yesterday, and How I’ve Been Recently</title><link href="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/10/26/today-yesterday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Today, Yesterday, and How I’ve Been Recently" /><published>2021-10-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/10/26/today-yesterday</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/10/26/today-yesterday/">&lt;p&gt;The past few weeks have gone really well for me. I started doing freelance software dev, met a lot of great people, and honestly life has felt a lot better. Now I have an actual job lined up and things are looking good. The folks at &lt;a href=&quot;https://studioarchetype.net&quot;&gt;Studio Archetype&lt;/a&gt; are great people to work with!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday was different… I woke up with PTSD-inducing flashbacks from my childhood, which arguably wasn’t great. I’ll spare you the details but it took me so long to get out of bed that I missed the fun day I had planned with a friend. Throughout the day I continued to have these flashbacks and it hasn’t felt good. I also confessed to my crush yesterday and have not recieved a response which kind of made it harder, but that’s okay; everybody needs time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning at 00:30 I went on a drive to clear my head, which is something I haven’t had to do in months. When I used to do it I would speed pretty heavily and I’d be out for a long time, but this time I just kinda cruised around town for 30 minutes. It’s 01:27 at the time of this sentence and I really don’t know what’s going on. My plan is to sleep and hopefully tomorrow will be easier.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Life" /><summary type="html">The past few weeks have gone really well for me. I started doing freelance software dev, met a lot of great people, and honestly life has felt a lot better. Now I have an actual job lined up and things are looking good. The folks at Studio Archetype are great people to work with!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Being Sick Isn’t Fun</title><link href="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/10/10/being-sick/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Being Sick Isn’t Fun" /><published>2021-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/10/10/being-sick</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/10/10/being-sick/">&lt;p&gt;I am sick as a dog right now. It’s actually difficult to write because I don’t get much time in between bathroom breaks or blowing my nose. Fact is, I don’t get sick very easily and right now I am showing COVID symptoms. &lt;em&gt;I’m vaccinated.&lt;/em&gt; It’s not often that I write anything political, but this warrants a little bit of analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, you know who isn’t vaccinated and also happens to work at Walmart? My rooommate. His reasoning is the standard “I want to know what they’re putting in my body” bullshit. It’s the “Oh I’m not a sheep” thinking that kills me the most. So you’re going to reject an FDA-approved vaccine because you think taking it will classify you as a sheep? I’m sorry, but not taking it simply because people you agree with tell you not to IS WHAT A SHEEP DOES.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At some point, getting vaccinated needs to not be about politics and it needs to be about saving people’s fucking lives. I am going to the pharmacy where I got my vaccination to request another card, just in case I have to go to the ER. The only reason I wanta copy of my vax card is that some places are finally doing what they shouldv’e done a long time ago and refusing people who aren’t vaccinated beds. I will also get tested, just to make sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact that people put others’ lives at risk because of differences in their political beliefs is astonishing to me. Why? I don’t know, honestly. It isn’t anything new, so it shouldn’t astonish me; I guess I’m just surprised by the scale of it with COVID-19 involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think I need to elaborate on what makes the “I need to know what they’re putting in my body” argument absolutely worthless. A lot of what the FDA does approve is not safe as it is, yet the same people arguing against the vaccine &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;eat this kind of shit all the time&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. A solid example is Taco Bell’s beef. That shit &lt;em&gt;barely&lt;/em&gt; meets FDA standards and I don’t see these people trying to get Taco Bell shut down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another common argument I see (and one my roommate has used) is that the vaccine isn’t 100%. &lt;em&gt;That is how a vaccine works.&lt;/em&gt; No vaccine is 100%, and it is proven that the a vaccine greatly reduces the risk of catching it, the symptoms &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; the risk of death from the disease. I don’t remember the exact statistics but I encourage everyone reading this to do their own research because that is how we keep information in check. &lt;em&gt;It’s called fact-checking. Learn how to do it and do it properly for the love of god.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, if you do not want to get a COVID-19 vaccine, it is &lt;strong&gt;your&lt;/strong&gt; decision. BUT, if you go outside without a mask, stay the fuck away from the rest of us who are doing our part to keep this virus from spreading. Herd immunity is a thing. I heard an interesting analogy that goes something like “If all of your friends told you to jump off a cliff would you?” being used as an argument against the vaccine, and my response is this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;No. What you refer to is backwards thinking anyways. &lt;em&gt;You are actively jumping off a cliff while being told not to.&lt;/em&gt; You may think “Fine, my life my decision”, but you also fail to understand that you are tied to everybody else, and everyone is on the edge of this cliff. If enough of you motherfuckers jump, &lt;em&gt;you pull all the rest of us down with you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t jump.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Life" /><category term="Current Events" /><summary type="html">I am sick as a dog right now. It’s actually difficult to write because I don’t get much time in between bathroom breaks or blowing my nose. Fact is, I don’t get sick very easily and right now I am showing COVID symptoms. I’m vaccinated. It’s not often that I write anything political, but this warrants a little bit of analysis. But, you know who isn’t vaccinated and also happens to work at Walmart? My rooommate. His reasoning is the standard “I want to know what they’re putting in my body” bullshit. It’s the “Oh I’m not a sheep” thinking that kills me the most. So you’re going to reject an FDA-approved vaccine because you think taking it will classify you as a sheep? I’m sorry, but not taking it simply because people you agree with tell you not to IS WHAT A SHEEP DOES. At some point, getting vaccinated needs to not be about politics and it needs to be about saving people’s fucking lives. I am going to the pharmacy where I got my vaccination to request another card, just in case I have to go to the ER. The only reason I wanta copy of my vax card is that some places are finally doing what they shouldv’e done a long time ago and refusing people who aren’t vaccinated beds. I will also get tested, just to make sure. The fact that people put others’ lives at risk because of differences in their political beliefs is astonishing to me. Why? I don’t know, honestly. It isn’t anything new, so it shouldn’t astonish me; I guess I’m just surprised by the scale of it with COVID-19 involved. And I think I need to elaborate on what makes the “I need to know what they’re putting in my body” argument absolutely worthless. A lot of what the FDA does approve is not safe as it is, yet the same people arguing against the vaccine eat this kind of shit all the time. A solid example is Taco Bell’s beef. That shit barely meets FDA standards and I don’t see these people trying to get Taco Bell shut down. Another common argument I see (and one my roommate has used) is that the vaccine isn’t 100%. That is how a vaccine works. No vaccine is 100%, and it is proven that the a vaccine greatly reduces the risk of catching it, the symptoms and the risk of death from the disease. I don’t remember the exact statistics but I encourage everyone reading this to do their own research because that is how we keep information in check. It’s called fact-checking. Learn how to do it and do it properly for the love of god. At the end of the day, if you do not want to get a COVID-19 vaccine, it is your decision. BUT, if you go outside without a mask, stay the fuck away from the rest of us who are doing our part to keep this virus from spreading. Herd immunity is a thing. I heard an interesting analogy that goes something like “If all of your friends told you to jump off a cliff would you?” being used as an argument against the vaccine, and my response is this: No. What you refer to is backwards thinking anyways. You are actively jumping off a cliff while being told not to. You may think “Fine, my life my decision”, but you also fail to understand that you are tied to everybody else, and everyone is on the edge of this cliff. If enough of you motherfuckers jump, you pull all the rest of us down with you. Don’t jump.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Brain Mush</title><link href="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/09/30/brain-mush/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Brain Mush" /><published>2021-09-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-09-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/09/30/brain-mush</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/09/30/brain-mush/">&lt;p&gt;In the past, I used to go in and out of cycles where I would make software for so long, and then the other part of the year I would primarily play games. The past year or so has been different. I haven’t been able to motivate myself to do anything code-related and I feel like a large part of that is lack of motivation from my depression, and possibly the fact that for most of the year I was working a day job that killed me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On top of all this, I’ve started doing cannabis in the form of smoking and edibles to help cope with the fact that I’m just not the same. Self-deprecating humor is a very prevalent coping mechanism, too. It doesn’t help that my family is extremely abusive and I’m struggling to pay rent with a roommate. Oh and I quit my job, so no income. I wouldn’t have lasted anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s to the point where my brain is so fucked from the trauma I have had that my sense of time has warped dramatically; I’m worried my brain might just be beyond repair. I also don’t remember a lot of the things I used to, like my memory is just failing. My short-term memory is also bad. Basic logic is also becoming difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also feeling as if there is nothing I can do to be successful. The only time I feel happy is when others are happy because of me or what I do; I think I’ve lost all forms of self-gratification. This makes motivating myself to do things extremely hard. Loneliness is like gasoline in this infinite blaze of pain that just makes it bigger and worse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I applied (and got accepted) to local community college, so that’s nice I guess. When I announced the news to my parents, Dad was semi-excited but more concerned about what it meant for his wallet, and Mom just said “Well you’re probably just going to fail anyway”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess I just don’t know where to go from here. If you have any ideas of software I could work on, I’m &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Lizzy A#0001&lt;/code&gt; on Discord so tell me, I guess. I could use a distraction while I lose my mind.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Life" /><category term="Code" /><summary type="html">In the past, I used to go in and out of cycles where I would make software for so long, and then the other part of the year I would primarily play games. The past year or so has been different. I haven’t been able to motivate myself to do anything code-related and I feel like a large part of that is lack of motivation from my depression, and possibly the fact that for most of the year I was working a day job that killed me.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Moving Out</title><link href="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/05/26/moving-out/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Moving Out" /><published>2021-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/05/26/moving-out</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/05/26/moving-out/">&lt;p&gt;My parents have been threatening to kick me out for a while. It started when I was 17 and now that I’m 18 they have been more incessant about it. I found some roommates but we’re still looking for an apartment. Long story short, my parents finally freaked out a week ago and pulled the stunt. I ended up contacting my roommates and saying “Hey, can I stay with you guys a bit earlier than planned?” and I have been staying with them for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-living-situation&quot;&gt;My Living Situation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, my roommates (Wes And Michaela) are two married high school friends of mine, and they live with Wes’s family (who will be referred to by their initials). In their house are five other humans, four cats, and one dog. That makes eight humans including myself, and the animals. I’m currently sleeping in the fireplace room on a roll up bed. I have my basic necessities, and a car which I will discuss in a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-car&quot;&gt;The Car&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, my parents let me use a 2011 Chevy Aveo that used to be their business car to get around, but they made a very big deal about not letting me use it after moving out. Wes’s dad works around cars a lot and gets some good deals on vehicles. He happened to have an old Mercury Sable sitting around and offered to sell it to me on a pay-as-I-go basis for a total of $800 over four months. I took the offer and am currently using the car to get around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;downtime&quot;&gt;Downtime&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During my downtime, I have gone to the mall with Q (Wes’s nonbinary sibling) and Michaela, or I have helped Michaela with her blog, among other things (i.e. playing games). Today we went shopping at the 5 Below store and I got some perfume, then we went to the mall where I got some tights which are the cutest and most comfortable things I think I have ever worn. The feminine stuff I’m trying has also helped a lot with my dysphoria. Another thing that helped was that I got my ears pierced, which is cool. If you’re wondering what the fragrance is, it’s “Pink Candy”. A coworker of mine wears it and I had to ask “Where on earth did you get this and what is it called” because it’s such a good fragrance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wess-mom&quot;&gt;Wes’s Mom&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wes’s mom is, let’s say… special. She has her fair share of issues getting along with people, especially Q and Michaela. She seems to be okay with calling me by my preferred pronouns and name, but won’t respect those of Q, who is nonbinary and prefers they/them pronouns. Wes’s mom also has trouble treating Michaela kindly and that causes Michaela a lot of stress, not to mention strains the relationship. She also has trouble getting along with Wes’s younger brother, S. The only one she tends to get along with is R, Wes’s younger sister.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Life" /><summary type="html">My parents have been threatening to kick me out for a while. It started when I was 17 and now that I’m 18 they have been more incessant about it. I found some roommates but we’re still looking for an apartment. Long story short, my parents finally freaked out a week ago and pulled the stunt. I ended up contacting my roommates and saying “Hey, can I stay with you guys a bit earlier than planned?” and I have been staying with them for a while.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Where do I go from here?</title><link href="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/05/08/where-to-go/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Where do I go from here?" /><published>2021-05-08T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-05-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/05/08/where-to-go</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/05/08/where-to-go/">&lt;p&gt;This past week has been hell for me, and I’ll cut to the chase: I don’t really know where I am going from here. I don’t really even know how to start writing about it, but I’ll do my best. It is also important to note that this is my side of the equation, and not meant to harm anyone at all. Essentially, I’m just venting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-first-week&quot;&gt;The First Week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A bit of context first. I don’t have a good relationship with my parents, and I just turned 18. Meaning the threats of being kicked out sting a lot more now than they did a year ago. This is very emotionally exhausting to deal with, especially for someone like myself, who is on the autistic spectrum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also worth mentioning that I have been in a romantic relationship since January, which will play into things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-start&quot;&gt;The Start&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My week started with a really awful Monday. I had a bad day at work, and as usual I get into a call with my boyfriend, because if I call someone else (friends, etc.) I’ll be dealing with a frustrated boyfriend. Same deal if I don’t call at all. What’s different this time, however, is that I had just attempted suicide on the way home. I don’t really know why, but I had a really strong, sudden urge to swerve off the road. I would’ve hit some cliffs and died had I not got a grip on my emotions and stopped the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the call, I had another urge and so I muted and deafened to try and OD on painkillers in the bathroom. Sometime during the call, my boyfriend had done some things on Twitter to instigate my friends, which was another reason I had been having suicidal ideations. I was tired of having to balance social and romantic life because my boyfriend couldn’t get along with my friends, or at least leave them alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day at work, suicidal thoughts were back, and I couldn’t stop it. I talked to some coworkers who were all concerned, and they suggested I cut it off, at least temporarily. So, that night when I got home, I told my boyfriend I couldn’t do a romantic relationship for the foreseeable future, but I was willing to remain friends. His response was “k”. The thing that hurt the most was that the night before in the call he told me that if he ever responded “k” or “okay” it meant he didn’t care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;off-days&quot;&gt;Off Days&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next two days I was off work, so I spent time with some friends. All of that was about as good as it could’ve been, given the circumstances. Certain things happened that I won’t mention, but nothing too terribly bad, just embarrassing stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;fri-yay&quot;&gt;Fri “yay”&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, on Friday, my dad gave me thirty days to find a place to live. This is why I don’t really know where I can go from here. I have to figure out how I’m going to pay for a place, food, and everything else important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;update-on-relesase-i-guess&quot;&gt;Update On Relesase, I Guess&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wrote all of that above on Sunday the 2nd. It is now Saturday the 8th and oh my god it gets worse (and better, kinda). I feel like a nuisance, and honestly a dipshit. Over the past few days, it has gotten harder and harder to get along with people, even the people I care about and I’m considering just giving up socially. White flag of surrender and never speak to people again, essentially. I can’t go five minutes without pissing someone else off and I feel terrible every time I talk to people. That being said, someone sent $100 to my PayPal today with a message “Go get some salt chips and an apartment”. While that $100 won’t cover an entire apartment it will help a whole lot with the deposit; so thanks to whoever sent it, it feels a little bit less painful to be alive right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-future&quot;&gt;The Future&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess I’ll be moving out soon. I don’t know what else, and honestly I can’t motivate myself to do anything at all; we’ll see. Right now I just want things to mellow out and I think it might happen soon. Aside from that, I’m hoping I can motivate myself to get back to work on Synapse, and I’m finding it somewhat easier to do things I once enjoyed. I haven’t had suicidal ideations since the night that I attempted twice, so that feels good. I guess I’ll just have to wait and see how things go socially though.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Life" /><summary type="html">This past week has been hell for me, and I’ll cut to the chase: I don’t really know where I am going from here. I don’t really even know how to start writing about it, but I’ll do my best. It is also important to note that this is my side of the equation, and not meant to harm anyone at all. Essentially, I’m just venting.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Name, and Some Euphoric Vibes</title><link href="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/03/21/a-name/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Name, and Some Euphoric Vibes" /><published>2021-03-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/03/21/a-name</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/03/21/a-name/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-importance-of-a-name&quot;&gt;The Importance of a Name&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A name is the most important part of who you are. Without a name, you are nobody. If nobody knows your name, you’re nobody. But the right name can make all the difference. That’s why it’s difficult changing it, but when you’re transgender it is often a necessary change to make. For me, I went from Landon (my given name) to Liz, which is my preferred name. It’s taken a lot of getting used to but I am gaining more confidence with it every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-change&quot;&gt;The Change&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When picking a new name, I wanted to keep my first initial the same so I had an L name. I started rattling off names until I found one I really liked - Liz. I thought “How does this represent me?” then I came up with the fact that “Liz” is also the start to the word “lizard”, and lizards are cute (like I hope to be) and resilient (like I am emotionally). I thought this represented me pretty well, so I went with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;my-name-tag&quot;&gt;My Name Tag&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got a new name tag today with my new name on it. I also let everyone at work know my preferred name and my she/her pronoun preference. The euphoric vibes didn’t stop all day and still haven’t. Here’s a picture of my new name tag:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/photos/2021-03-22_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My Name Tag&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Life" /><category term="LGBT" /><summary type="html">The Importance of a Name A name is the most important part of who you are. Without a name, you are nobody. If nobody knows your name, you’re nobody. But the right name can make all the difference. That’s why it’s difficult changing it, but when you’re transgender it is often a necessary change to make. For me, I went from Landon (my given name) to Liz, which is my preferred name. It’s taken a lot of getting used to but I am gaining more confidence with it every day.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tales From Walmart, Ep. 1</title><link href="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/03/20/tales-from-walmart/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tales From Walmart, Ep. 1" /><published>2021-03-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/03/20/tales-from-walmart</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/03/20/tales-from-walmart/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;preface&quot;&gt;Preface&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a new thing I have been wanting to do for a while. I work at a local Walmart Neighborhood Market and by God, some of the stuff that happens is just crazy. Of course this is mostly written as a recap and always written from a non-agressive standpoint, whether it be humorous or annoying or just plain confusing. I’ll try to write these somewhat frequently, but this one will likely be longer as there is a lot more material I have to utilize from the past 5 months. Of course, not all that material will go into this one post, but more of it should appear in later ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;eggs-with-a-pavement-wish&quot;&gt;Eggs with a Pavement Wish&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I clock out at the end of the day yesterday, and grab a carton of eggs. (a local farm gives some walmart associates the extra eggs or some shit. I dunno I just get eggs) On my way out, I walk up to Daniel, who I have been joking with all day, and say “suck an SSD”. His response was “I hope you drop your eggs in the parking lot and out of reflex kick them to break the fall” and I lost it. I just about started howling like a hyena. I could barely utter “That is literally the most douchebag thing you could’ve possibly said.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-antisocial-club&quot;&gt;The Antisocial Club&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The day before yesterday, I monitored self checkouts all day. I went to clean the far left one and a dude walks up, sets his stuff down and I go “How are you today?”. Without saying a word, the dude &lt;em&gt;immediately&lt;/em&gt; picked his stuff up off the belt and walked to the far end of the self checkouts to begin checking out, all the while looking over his shoulder to make sure we weren’t watching him. Spoiler alert: we were.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tale-of-10000-bananas-not-actually&quot;&gt;Tale of 10,000 Bananas (Not Actually)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, in the first week or so I worked at Walmart, I had a dude come through the self checkouts and ring up 10 bananas, each on its own transaction. I was thinking “Either this dude’s a legend or he’s incredibly stupid.” It turned out to be a little bit of both: he was a legend because he was able to do it all masterfully without an issue, and he was incredibly stupid because the reason he was doing it was because apparently some credit card companies give you some amount of cash if you make a certain amount of transactions each month. Uhh, hello? The Google Play store exists for a reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;grand-theft-asparagus&quot;&gt;Grand Theft Asparagus&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About early February, I was monitoring self checkouts, and my coworker Judah, who was monitoring the other half of the self checkouts, comes over and says “So we just had grand theft asparagus over here.” I cracked up and asked him to clarify. He goes “Well they walked out with $20 worth of asparagus after ringing it up”. Yeah, That much asparagus should last them quite some time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Tales From Walmart" /><category term="Life" /><summary type="html">Preface This is a new thing I have been wanting to do for a while. I work at a local Walmart Neighborhood Market and by God, some of the stuff that happens is just crazy. Of course this is mostly written as a recap and always written from a non-agressive standpoint, whether it be humorous or annoying or just plain confusing. I’ll try to write these somewhat frequently, but this one will likely be longer as there is a lot more material I have to utilize from the past 5 months. Of course, not all that material will go into this one post, but more of it should appear in later ones.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Leveling Up</title><link href="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/01/24/leveling-up/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Leveling Up" /><published>2021-01-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-01-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/01/24/leveling-up</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/01/24/leveling-up/">&lt;p&gt;I always thought I’d spend the entirety of my days lonely and depressed. I might’ve been wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was younger, it was extremely difficult for me to imagine myself having a significant other. I didn’t have any friends as it was, so I decided dating would belong on the back burner. In my sophomore year of high school, that began to change. I moved to public school and almost immediately started making friends. I also found the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I first signed up for Discord, I never expected it to become as big of a part of my life as it is. To be fair, I didn’t really know much about the internet then. (I learned pretty quickly) Since I have been on Discord, I have made more friends than I could ever imagine myself having as a kid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, let’s cut to the chase. I won’t be using actual names for privacy reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A while back, I joined a Discord for Minecraft shaders. I met a certain person there who I really enjoyed talking to. I then distanced myself from the server because of how poorly managed it was. Well… I’m also in a lot of servers revolving around the OptiFine community, and I was pleasantly surprised when I saw the certain someone from the shader server had joined a small private server I was in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a few voice chats, I began to feel something special… it’s hard to describe, but I describe it more or less as a crush. So I wrote a small C++ program to print a message to standard output, with these lines:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;I might have a crush on you...
I know this isn't too impressive but my creativity is nonexistent :)
 - Lizzy
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then sent it to him, and had him run it. My anxiety has kicked in by this time. We talked in DM, and he said he likes to go slowly with this kind of thing, which I am perfectly okay with. We decided to stay friends for the time, and move ahead from there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next night it was voice chat again. We spend about 6 hours exchanging memes and laughing way too hard at some of them. But at the end of the call, it was time for him to go to bed. Here’s a blurred screenshot of our DM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/screenshots/2021-01/discord_0001.png&quot; alt=&quot;The DM&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It may not seem like much, but the thing about this is, I’ve never met a person who likes me for me. The feeling of happiness still hasn’t gone away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of this being said, what’s going on is in its very early stages. I’m currently playing it by ear and moving forward one step at a time. But it’s given me hope, which is more of what this post is about.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Life" /><category term="Internet" /><summary type="html">I always thought I’d spend the entirety of my days lonely and depressed. I might’ve been wrong.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Frustrations With Electron and Webpack</title><link href="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/01/07/electron-webpack-frustrations/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Frustrations With Electron and Webpack" /><published>2021-01-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-01-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/01/07/electron-webpack-frustrations</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lizainslie.dev/blog/2021/01/07/electron-webpack-frustrations/">&lt;p&gt;So, a while back, I created a moderately popular app called MyRPC. (It’s dead now) Essentially, it was a custom status application for Discord based on the RPC function of Discord. At the time of its creation, my knowledge was mostly of Node.js, so I opted to use Electron. The earliest versions of the code worked spectacularly, and the app was a  hit. However, I learned React at some point, and decided that MyRPC could use a touch of React. Bearing in mind that &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;create-react-app&lt;/code&gt; was essentially the only way to do React at the time (unless you wanted to configure everything manually), I opted to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All was well, until I ran into some issues. (classic Node.js fairy-tale, right?) The Discord RPC worked fine, however what really hurt was the build process. I wanted to have cross-platform builds without having to know someone with a Mac and someone with a Linux installation, so I setup Travis CI and AppVeyor (for Windows because Travis CI’s Windows support was sketchy at best). Here’s where it got murky (and it’s also why I keep my distance from most CI/CD pipelines). I wanted to do a few things with CI:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Build an installer for each platform.&lt;/strong&gt; This wasn’t too big of a problem after I got the build scripts fine-tuned.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create and tag a GitHub release on __tagged commits only__.&lt;/strong&gt; It wasn’t too difficult to do this either. The hard parts were:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Determining whether or not the commit was tagged.&lt;/strong&gt; Git isn’t too nice about this. &lt;em&gt;Something, something, platform specific string parsing…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creating only one release.&lt;/strong&gt; Travis and AppVeyor each had a different idea of how to generate a release name. And even if the names were the same, I still had problems getting AppVeyor to simply update the release if it already existed rather than just failing the job.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upload the built installers to the new release.&lt;/strong&gt; TL;DR, directory structures suck.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use the tagged commit’s message as the release description.&lt;/strong&gt; Simply put, you should &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; attempt this. You will, by every guarantee, spend hours on end trying to get it to work properly and never succeed. Good luck.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My frustration was mostly with the process. Between these steps, I was losing my mind:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Compile the UI with Webpack. Hope and pray to our lord and savior Satan that the Electron renderer module is accessible to the UI code.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Run the Electron app. Hope that it can find the Webpack output, and if it can’t, start packing your bags for Brazil.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If all of the above works… well, here comes the fun part. Commit all your changes, tag the latest commit (if it’s a release), and push that code.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Go fix the 1,000 issues that Travis CI and AppVeyor have when trying to build the app, and make damn sure they upload the installers to the same release.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Describe the release, because no matter how hard you try you can never seem to get Travis to pull the commit content and put it in the release description.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This should not have been so difficult, but alas: Electron.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Rants" /><category term="Tech" /><category term="Code" /><category term="JavaScript" /><category term="Git" /><summary type="html">So, a while back, I created a moderately popular app called MyRPC. (It’s dead now) Essentially, it was a custom status application for Discord based on the RPC function of Discord. At the time of its creation, my knowledge was mostly of Node.js, so I opted to use Electron. The earliest versions of the code worked spectacularly, and the app was a hit. However, I learned React at some point, and decided that MyRPC could use a touch of React. Bearing in mind that create-react-app was essentially the only way to do React at the time (unless you wanted to configure everything manually), I opted to use it.</summary></entry></feed>